[Footsteps, Gasping]
[Gasping]
Oh,
my God.
No, oh
[Screaming] Somebody, help!
[Screaming, gunshot]
[Loud thud]
[Groaning]
[Labored breathing]
Make it stop,
please!
[Gunshot]
[Slow rock music]
[Music continues]
[Country music playing]
♪ Come on baby baby
won't you let me in, ♪
♪ Love me once you can
love me again. ♪
♪ Won't you let me in? ♪
♪ Baby, let me in. ♪
♪ Open up,
and I'm up to you... ♪
Beautiful night,
don't you think?
Can't you take
a hint and get lost?
You can walk away
with something.
[Country music continues
in the background]
[Snaps paper]
[Money rustling]
We can make this
easier on everyone.
♪ I'm begging you,
don't say don't. ♪
♪ Come away, you got my heart. ♪
[Applause] - Thank you!
Is Jack in on this?!
[Footsteps]
You don't give a rat's ass
what anybody says to you.
I don't like where
this is going.
No woman's gonna come
between me and my family.
[Bangs table]
What are you doing?
Hey!
Come on.
[Grunting, whimpering]
[Struggling]
Fucking cunt.
Give me back my 20 grand.
Jack, stop. Jack, stop!
Fucking kill you.
I hear that knock.
The little Scotsman knows
who makes him stand.
I ought to fucking...
It isn't Mrs. thin...
[Spits on the ground]
Mrs. Fucking thinlips.
[Whimpers]
Get ready for 1980!
[Crowd shouts]
10, 9, 8,
7, 6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1,
Happy New Year!
[Cheering and applause]
[Kissing] Mmm...
[Sobbing]
Your day as shitty as mine.
[Crying, whimpering]
Name's Doug Clark.
Oh.
[Whimpering continues]
Carol Mary Bundy.
Carol for short.
I'm not really the person
you're thinking of.
[Chuckles] - That's
good to know.
So uh,
why so blue on New Year's Eve?
It's just too late.
It's never too late.
[Country music]
You want to dance?
Uh huh.
You don't wear a ring.
Are you married?
Nope.
No longer a member of that club.
Me either.
I'm still friendly with
my ex, though.
That's a rarity.
What do you do, Miss Carol?
I'm a nurse,
you?
I'm a sound engineer.
Sound engineer.
What does that mean?
Well, we make pro
audio equipment,
we mix records,
and we dub bad kung fu movies.
[Chuckles]
Bad kung fu movies.
Yeah.
A man with a wooden leg,
has the right of way.
[Music continues
in the background]
Happy New Year.
[Grunts, kissing]
[Soft groans]
[Breathing heavily]
♪ I'm gonna take it in my
pocket. And a feeling in my
bones. ♪
♪ Life is a desert. ♪
♪ Love is a storm. ♪
♪ In this lonesome city. ♪
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
So this is where
you run off to, huh?
You bored with me already?
Heck no.
You're the king of conversation.
I think I had a little too
much champagne.
Your place is lovely.
Lots of delicate
little things in a...
All the right places.
It's the last of your bourbon.
[Groans]
Do you believe in
love at first sight?
I do.
Sometimes you meet a person,
a shock goes
through you, like...
Lightning.
All your emotions just...
explode.
[Moaning softly]
[Both moaning]
[Excited whimpers]
[Chuckles]
[Belt clicks]
[Heavy breathing]
[Moaning softly]
How's that?
I'm not stopping you.
It's one of my specialties.
[Gasping heavily]
It's great.
It's okay.
Lets fucking fuck.
[Moaning]
Let's fucking fuck.
[Grunting, moaning]
[Music builds]
[Moaning, man grunting]
[Man grunting heavily]
[Man grunting, both moaning]
[Both breathing heavily]
[Upbeat guitar music]
Guess this pulls the curtain
down on our romance.
Can't imagine you ever
calling me again.
I'm not gonna stop calling you
until you tell me to
stop calling you.
Don't say that unless
you mean it.
You think I want some
bubble-headed bimbo,
with clown makeup?
I need somebody real.
I need somebody to talk to.
[Bed rustles]
[Kisses]
[Glass squeaking]
He manages this place.
Get out of my face.
[Glass squeaking continues]
Shit, fucking cock.
I need a shower.
[Glass squeaking outside]
[Foreboding music]
[Sighs]
[Sound effects]
TV: Hey look, another one!
Brother, there's
a boat over there.
All right, we'll draw alongside
and then we'll board it.
What do you suggest
we do with them?
Throw the old man into the
river, and we'll keep the girl.
Heh.
You agree?
[Laughing]
OK, that was pretty good.
How about a little less on
the extreme laughter?
Give me a little
more humor with it.
[Laughing loudly]
Spot on.
Recorder: Listen,
I guess those two bastards
...will make easy meat of them.
...Hey, one of them's coming.
[Foreboding music]
[Knocking]
[Music continues]
[Slaps arm]
[Sniffles]
[Groans in pain] - Ow!
Sorry
[Door opening]
[Music fades]
[Door closing]
Carol,
these are for you.
[Flowers rustling]
Oh.
Yeah.
Back for seconds.
Can you believe it?
Can you blame him?
Might be time to
retire the vibrator.
[Paper rustling]
[Man groaning]
Oh!, you just turned on tired.
Don't stop!
[Man groaning]
[Both moaning loudly]
Why do you make
me so fucking hot.
[Both moaning loudly]
[Breathing heavily]
What?
I'm just...
I'm impressed with
how alike we are.
We're both Libras.
[Chuckles]
[Moaning soflty]
Want me to unpack for you?
No, I got it.
I cleared out a few drawers,
made some space in the closet.
Hmm.
Hmm, thank you for that.
I'll cook steaks tomorrow night.
Open that nice
bottle of Chianti.
Hmm.
Do me a favor.
Huh?
Keep mine a little pink.
[Chuckles]
[Upbeat country music]
♪ I'm gonna ride that train, ♪
♪ ride that train,
ride that train, ♪
♪ away from you. ♪
♪ I'm gonna ride that train
right away from my pain, ♪
♪ the pain that I give
in loving you. ♪
♪ You ain't no good, ♪
♪ you ain't no good. ♪
[Foreboding music]
[Ominous music continues]
[Foreboding music continues]
[Recorder: Please,
please don't, please...]
[...Please don't
do it! Please!]
[Gunshot, groaning]
No, please! [Gunshot]
[Ominous music continues]
[Recorder clicks]
[Key opening lock]
[Footsteps]
[Bed rustling]
[Creaking wood boards]
Hmm, hot.
[Moaning]
Oh, baby.
You're so sexy.
[Both moaning]
[Kissing]
[Moaning softly]
[Moaning continues]
[Moaning, grunting]
[Moans in pain] Ow!
Jesus, wildcat!
You're making a fucking
meal out of me.
Sorry.
For crying out loud!
It's okay, Doug!
I know it's okay.
I'm gonna get a beer.
You want a beer?
No, I didn't come here to drink.
I made you dinner.
I expected you hours ago.
Just calm down,
little funky spy.
I need a little
attitude adjustment.
time got away from you, okay?
That's it.
Wait.
Baby,
you can't think I'm as attracted
to her as I am to you.
I... I want her to leave.
Oh, Dougie, might I help
you with anything in there?
No, no, I'm out in a sec. I'm
just, gotta find the opener.
All right.
Be out in a sec.
Dougie, can I help you?
You need any help out there?
Hey, hey, hey.
She's a fucking sack of
potatoes to me, okay?
You better cut it with this
boohoo crybaby crap.
You wanna keep acting
like my fucking parents?
That is a serious insecurity,
and I will be fucking out
of here in the morning.
Is that what you want? No
more fucking calls from me.
No more letters.
No more nothing.
Me out of your life forever,
particularly now that fucking
singing cowboy's gone.
I don't want to be...
I don't want to be second
or third on your list.
I want to be number one.
You are. You are.
This is humiliating.
No, no, no, baby, it isn't.
It's a quirk.
A quirk of mine.
Go with it. Go with it.
And you and I got
a beautiful future, okay?
[Whimpering]
[Music]
[Kissing]
Go with it.
[Sobs]
Do you mind if we use the bed?
Because the sofa's
a little lumpy.
I'll just...
I'll just hang out in here.
Now that,
is secure.
[Whimpers]
[Kisses]
Okay, baby, I'm coming in now.
Just got the opener, and uh...
took me a little while.
Sorry about that.
Ooh, my wildcat!
Oh, you're a foxy man.
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
What am I doing?
This in my fucking apartment?
Fuck it, fuck it, fuck it!
[Jazzy music]
[Door creaking]
[Climbing stairs, footsteps]
[Door opening]
Sure, sure. Okay.
Okay, that sounds fine.
Yes.
I'll call again later.
Bye-bye.
[Paper bag rustling]
[Box thuds]
[Can thuds on cupboard]
[Refrigerator door opens]
[Door closes]
Jesus, you scared me.
[Sighs]
There's bourbon in the bag.
[Clears throat]
I bet the farm you've got me
pegged as asshole of
the century,
after last night.
Whatever makes you happy, Doug.
My mouth moves ahead
of my brain sometimes.
I didn't mean to offend you.
Oh.
Oh. It doesn't matter.
It does.
There's a little uh,
Hollywood party tonight.
Movie star friend of mine.
Interested?
Obviously.
[Moaning]
[Moaning softly]
[Slapping sound]
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I wanted to see
that look on your face.
[Chuckles softly]
Dougie, you made it!
Who's the babe?
Carol, I'd like you to
meet John Holmes.
Gangbang on the New York
subway's the next setup.
See anything you like
back there, Carol?
They're here to dip their wicks,
and we got some
damn fine coke, too.
Let me know when you're ready.
What's the name of the movie?
Oh, Nixon Nails the Nymphos.
Join in, watch whatever.
I'm up.
Get the fuck in there!
We don't got all day!
Action!
I am not a crook!
This is real sexual
freedom, baby.
[Moaning, groaning]
It's raw. Beautiful.
So are you.
That's why you're here.
[Moaning continues
in the background]
[Chuckles soflty]
[Car engine rumbles]
[Breaks squealing softly]
[Car door opens]
My boobs feel free to
the first time I got them.
Oh,
Freedom, huh?
That's what I am all about.
I got it.
It's okay. I... I owe him.
He made me get a second
opinion on my eyes.
Yeah
He's a predator who preys
on weak minds.
I'd be blind without him.
Lie about your wife's cancer,
to scam Carol's money?
What?
Ooh, that's rich.
Mind your own beeswax, mate.
Oh...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I bet he stole,
and spent all of Carol's
settlement at the track,
and didn't give any to
you and your daughter,
did you?
You pussy.
You make me puke.
Fuck off, dickhead.
Basically, the mortar shell
that's coming down around you,
doesn't have any eyes,
ears, or assholes.
And it's gonna hurt.
Pay her back.
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
Jack!
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Hi honey.
What time is it?
Listen, ready for
something way out there?
Huh?
You hooked a fish?
[Chuckles softly]
Who are you talking to, Dougie?
It's my accountant.
Well, tell him it's last call...
...you are buying
me another drink.
...Sure, baby.
Don't let anybody take my seat.
[Chuckles]
[Whispering] -...She's
another skirt. Inconsequential.
I know.
Hold the camera straight.
...I don't want a bunch
of blurry shots.
They won't be blurry.
Trust me.
...You're the best.
...I'm about to reel in
a wide-mouth bass, baby.
Good luck, Doug.
[Hangs up]
[Melancholic music playing]
Oh sheesh.
So this is my humble abode.
My cousin Marisol loves clowns.
Oh.
Oh, I mean,
everybody loves a clown.
Why not you?
[Chuckles]
Do the tipsy dance.
Hmm...
Aah.
There it is.
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
[Chuckles]
[Moaning softly]
[Breathing heavily]
[Camera clicks]
Oh, my God!
What? What is it?
What?
The woman was
taking our picture!
Oh, come on. What
are you talking about?
Oh my God, yes, yes!
No, wait, hey look,
I need some...
I'm gonna shove that woman's
camera so far up her ass.
I know five-year-olds
that are more mature than...
Was she the accountant
you were talking to?
No, but I can't...
I see how this works now.
Would you keep your fucking
voice down, please?
You're sick in the head pervert.
Ow! God damn it!
Fucking Heinrich Himmler
has got nothing on you.
Hey, you know what? I bite back.
[Opens door]
[Music]
[Whimpering]
Smell this! Smell
this! Smell it! Smell it!
You smell that? She was
ready to take it in the ass.
[Groaning]
[Groaning angrily]
[Moaning in pain]
Now, wake up
the neighborhood tonight, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
Make some noise, baby.
[Moaning in pain]
[Grunting angrily]
[Moaning painfully]
[Groaning]
[Phone ringing]
[Phone clicks]
Hello?
I agree to obey any
order from my master.
I submit to any punishment
my master sees fit.
Once I started typing,
the words just poured out.
I agree to put on or take off,
any article of clothing or
instrument of bondage,
my master commands.
A slave contract.
Whatever it takes
to prove my love.
Hmm, that's a good start.
What are you up to?
Preparing your favorite dinner.
Roast chicken.
Yeah.
Wait.
Don't tell me you're off to
Shamu the Killer Whales tonight.
No.
Some of the guys are getting
together to watch a game,
so I just told them
I'd swing by.
Okay.
Fine.
By the by,
I'm wearing a pair
of your underwear.
They fit?
Oh.
Very comfy.
You should put on a pair
of mine sometime.
Okay, babe, I gotta go.
Love you.
Feelings mutual, baby. Bye-bye.
[Melancholic music playing]
[Country music playing]
[Car engine passing by]
Hey, ladies!
looking for a ride?
You two look like
fun loving tourists.
Let me guess.
Midwest.
Cleveland.
We're meeting a friend on
Doheny Drive in Beverly Hills.
You going that way?
Yeah.
I go where Cindy goes.
All right.
[Country music continues]
Blondie you're in front.
String bean in the back.
Name's Gina.
Okay.
Gina.
And we are not from
Cleveland either.
Okay.
Wrong city.
[Car pulls away]
[Country music fades]
[Faucet running]
[Glass clinks]
Doug?
[Tap running]
[Breathing heavily]
Carol.
[Heavy breathing]
[Doug trembling]
It's okay.
[Whimpering]
[Sobbing]
[Sobbing continues]
[Crying]
[Whimpers] No, no.
No.
[Tap water running] No.
No. [Slams door]
[Tap water running stops]
[Door creaks open]
[Breathing heavily]
Carol.
Do you believe in true love?
That real love,
means,
everything,
no matter what?
Yes.
Two girls,
Step sisters.
[Breathing heavily]
They fought.
They scratched.
They screamed.
[Grunting]
[Breathing heavily]
And then they stopped.
[Melancholic music plays]
I'm done.
[Melancholic music playing]
[Music continues]
Doug?
You really did that with
the dead girls?
The twins.
They pissed you off, so you...
Killed them.
Ah.
[Gunshot, splatters]
[Screams]
[Gunshot]
[Coughing, labored breathing]
They forgot who they were
dealing with.
Blondie started
talking too much.
Don't even get me going
on that string bean.
Where are they now?
An off ramp near Griffith Park.
Coyotes will eat well tonight.
Hmm.
How many Doug?
Ten
Maybe twelve.
All women?
Mostly ladies of the night.
You don't mean to be cruel.
It's just your nature.
Oh, don't tell anyone.
Or I will open you up from
belly button to sternum.
I will not, no.
No, never.
Oh, good.
Then you'll wake
up in the morning...
That's enough talk.
[Ominous music continues]
[Foreboding music playing]
Was one of them a blonde?
Was she wearing a pink jumpsuit?
Listen detective,
don't give this to
the media if you want me
to contact you again.
My ass will be on the line if my
boyfriend sees a news report.
Just a sec.
Did you clean the emesis basins?
Did you fold the linen?
Yes.
Your shoes need to be shined.
I'm back.
All right.
This, this may be the one,
or it might not.
Right, but you're not
helping me either.
You're not putting
my mind at ease.
[Hangs up phone]
Can I ask you something?
Of course, baby.
Doesn't any of this
bother your conscience?
You ever been to India?
No.
Well, that's where,
you learn about
the real worth of life.
People die in the streets
there every day.
Plague,
dysentery,
starvation.
They don't cry.
They stack them bodies
up and burn them.
Humans been dying of
nonsensical reasons,
since the day of the caveman.
Some plot of land.
I don't know,
some invisible god.
I mean, taking out
a few of these idiots
before the Russians start
dropping nukes on us,
ain't gonna make
a dent in history.
You sure you're ready for this?
I work at a hospital.
I've seen death.
Mm-hmm.
[Gawking]
Oh God, that smell.
[Laughing]
It is ripe. Whoo!
I call her the brush bunny.
She made me chase her through
the brush to get her.
Look at over here.
Look at her cheek here.
I diced it up real nice so
the maggots wouldn't struggle.
[Chuckles]
What a skilled surgeon you are.
[Camera clicking]
How long's she been out here?
I don't know. Three, four weeks.
I like to check in on my girls
every once in a while, you know?
[Inhales deeply]
[Exhales]
Let them know how
special they are.
[Gunshots]
I love you.
[Music]
[Laughing]
[Rock music fades out]
[Recorder: Oh fuck!
Please don't run!]
[Come on, baby!]
[- It's for posterity.
- Ow!]
[Ow!]
[Grunting]
[You're hurting me.]
[- You're nice!
- Oh, Uh.]
[Lauging]
[You think anyone
would try to help?]
[Laughing]
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
[Sinister laughter]
[Ominous music playing]
TV: Two men hunting for snakes,
made a grisly discovery
underneath this discarded
mattress.
TV: Police confirm
the same. 25 caliber pistol
...is the one used in
the Sunset Strip slayings,
...that have been terrorizing,
Los Angeles.
[Police siren in distance]
...Investigators say
a woman called in
...with credible
information about the two
...Huntington Beach victims,
and they urge her to call back,
...at 1-800-555-HELP.
TV: What's wrong with Dracula?
He's losing his monster power.
...So is
Frankenstein. Monsterizer!
[Door creaking]
[Door closing]
Hey.
Hey, Doug.
Everything all right?
I missed you.
Oh.
You're a sweetheart.
[Kisses] Move over.
Ah.
[Inhales deeply]
Watching something on the tube?
Just some crap.
Hmm.
[TV in the background]
Now that's a good
looking couple.
Look at that smile on your face.
[Giggles]
I had to let the guy
at Fox Photo have it.
He botched the entire
rest of the roll.
This is the only one
that made it through.
We look beautiful.
[TV in the background]
What an embarrassment
that peanut farmer,
president of ours is.
Thank God,
once Reagan gets elected,
the U.S. Will know I'm gonna
be the fucking laughing stock
of the world.
[TV in the background]
Do I look okay?
[Cuffs clinking]
Sit up.
Hold out your hands.
[Cuffing]
Now you look extra beautiful.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
On your stomach,
on the bed.
Aah.
[Whip cracks]
Yeah.
You fucking take it!
[Whip cracks]
[Whip cracks,
groaning in pain] Take it!
Tell me you fucking love
it! [Whipping continues]
[Whip cracks]
[Breathing heavily]
What's it like to kill someone?
[Music]
It's silent,
and a roar.
It's a spotlight and a blackout
all at the same time.
You feel like you can fly.
Sounds liberating.
[Chuckles]
You get it.
I didn't know if you would.
[Gasps]
You said it before.
Our minds think alike.
Yeah.
Come with me next time.
My ultimate fantasy is to have
the woman I love kill for me.
I... I... I can't.
Wish I could...
[Paper rustles]
I agree to obey every command.
I agree to serve my master
however he sees fit.
Those your words?
Yeah.
It's total bullshit, then.
[Music]
What if we get caught?
We're not gonna get
caught. I'm untouchable.
And if it blows up?
I'll take the fall.
I'm just gonna tell 'em you're
some bimbo who doesn't
know shit from Shinola.
Do you trust me?
More than anybody.
Then stop hesitating.
We've only got
a few wild years left.
Let's use them.
Use the fear.
Turn it into power.
Look at me!
Some people deserve
to be eliminated.
[Whimpering]
Like Aussie man Jack.
We can get away with anything
as long as we believe in us.
[Exhales]
Okay. Okay, I'll go. I'll go.
I knew you had fire
in you. I knew it.
Sit up!
Hold your hands out. Sit up!
Take it.
You never aim it,
unless you're ready to kill.
Look at me.
That's your target.
Eyes on that.
Eyes on it.
Steady your hand.
Deep breaths.
You're gonna pull the trigger,
not yank it.
Kill that fucker.
[Gun clicks]
I love you more than anybody.
And I love you.
You're gonna make me so proud.
[Slow rock music]
There's a construction site,
up off Doheny.
The girls there like to play.
If you're in,
give me a signal.
What kind of a signal?
Baby, am I ever having a blast?
Baby, am I having a blast?
Perfect.
Stick to the script.
Never improvise.
I obey my leader.
[Music continues]
[Car pulls over]
Took a wrong turn to
Disneyland, Sugar?
Are you available?
[Car idles in the background]
[Car door opening]
I'm Pete. This is Melissa.
[Car door closes]
[Car pulls away]
[Slow rock music playing]
[Car engine rumbles]
[Rock music fades]
Does it bother you?
Him being a dirty dog?
Hey,
Melissa and I are into
open relationships.
I was asking Melissa.
This is nothing but sex.
Love is love.
If you say so.
Where's the money?
Business first.
Leave it on the dash.
Fair enough.
Uhmm... is not gonna take long.
Wanna park it outside?
I wanna watch.
Okay.
Undo your pants?
First I want a kiss.
Ha ha
Save the germ
exchange for Melissa.
You could be a human
before you're a hooker.
You want me to
step out of the car,
or do you want a blow?
A blow.
Good.
Undo your pants.
[Sighs]
[Moaning]
Yeah.
Little more teeth.
Baby am I having a blast?
At least one of us...
Is this a fucking joke?
Do it!
[Gunshot]
I knew you wouldn't
fucking do it!
I went through the whole
fucking thing with you!
I'm sorry.
Breathe! Steady hand!
Aim!
Pull!
Don't fucking yank the trigger!
How fucking hard is it?
I just got nervous. I'm sorry.
You got nervous?
You got... There are no
nerves in this game!
Alright,
we got a second stage here.
So gather your fucking shit
together and let's do it right.
Sure.
If you fuck this up again,
if you fuck this next part up,
I will leave you in
the fucking ditch.
No, no, no.
I will fucking...
slice you up.
I will do it right.
She really did have
one peach of an ass.
[Thuds]
[Foreboding music]
[Car door open and close]
[Car pulls away]
[Foreboding music continues]
[Faucet running]
Towel.
[Faucet turns off]
It sure is hard to get blood
out from under your nails.
Maybe I'll cut them.
My mom used to take such
good care of her nails.
Buffing them,
painting them pink.
Tonight wasn't the big
turn-off I expected.
It was like watching a movie.
Let... Let's do it again.
Shall I...
Shall I kill.
Shall I prepare
a kill-back for tomorrow?
You think this is a game?
What if she escaped?
I don't fucking trust you.
Hey,
I got confused.
Give me another chance?
Nope. Dismissed.
You were in my unit.
You'd be fucking
court-marshalled.
Oh, that's so unfair.
[Chuckles]
I gave you the signal.
Why didn't you shoot,
bitch, huh?
Were you looking for an out?
No, I swear.
When the hazard lights flash,
that's when you fire.
Right between the fucking eyes.
Is there anything
we have talked about,
that has gotten through,
in that fucking pea-sized,
brain of yours?
I got confused.
I mean, I was nervous.
You're a gutless worm.
You'll never get it.
You'll never be
anything in life.
You're a fraud.
I've ruined everything.
Just shoot me, end it!
You're so fucking
good at it, right?!
You know what?
You want off yourself,
you go ahead.
I don't care.
But this whole fucking thing,
us, is over.
Where are you going?
To walk the cat.
We don't have a cat. When
are you coming back?
I am not coming back.
Doug, please, I'm sorry.
You don't mean that.
I'll get it right next time,
I promise.
[Melancholic music playing]
[Sobbing softly]
[Music continues]
[Sighs]
[Upbeat country guitar music]
[Music continues]
♪ I was born inside
a hard rock, ♪
♪ My daddy was a stone. ♪
♪ I was born inside
a hard rock, ♪
♪ My daddy was a stone. ♪
♪ And I fell down
on the highway... ♪
Radio: Hikers in
the Malibu Hills...
...found the body of an
unidentified woman this morning.
...She'd been shot
once in the head.
...Police are working
to learn who she was
and how she ended up in...
[Keys in lock]
[Door creaks open]
[Door closing]
Good morning, Doug.
You were right to be upset.
I blew it.
If I talk about this right now,
I might kill someone.
I won't lose focus again.
You...
Were more than sloppy.
You're everything to me.
I give...
everything.
To you.
[Whimpers]
Whatever it takes.
Whatever.
I'm fucking going to bed, Carol.
♪ Hold me close.♪
Okay.
♪ Hold me tight. ♪
♪ Say you love me, ♪
♪ for tonight. ♪
♪ But in the morning, ♪
[Gunshot]
♪ come rain or shine, ♪
♪ I'll be gone. ♪
♪ I'm not a man. ♪
[Ominous music]
[Door closes]
[Door locks]
[Ominous music continues]
Gutless.
Not today.
[Struggling]
[Muffled screaming]
[Struggled breathing]
[Suspenseful music]
[Struggling continues,
muffled cries]
[Coughing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Door unlocks]
[Clears throat]
Why was this door locked, Carol?
The door wasn't locked, Doctor.
You know that's
against regulations.
I heard her scream.
Martha's disoriented again.
She thought I was her husband.
[Sobbing]
Martha, dear.
No, no, no, no. No, you know.
Easy. You're safe, dear.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Okay.
Alright
[Sobbing] - Murderer!
M..M..Murderer...
[Sobbing intensely]
Alright dear.
Okay.
Alright.
No sshh...
It's alright.
It's alright sweetheart.
You're safe in here.
Mur... mur.. murderer...
What?
Mu... Murde... rer
[Sobbing continues]
Easy sweetheart
You're fine, gonna be fine.
Don't worry.
No one's gonna hurt you.
[Crying continues]
[Ominous slow rock music]
[Foreboding music continues]
It's a piece of shit movie.
I mean, there was
no plot whatsoever.
It was romantic.
I liked it.
[Chuckles]
You are, Miss Average American.
What do you say we grab a drink?
Let's have us a time instead.
Forget it.
I can't count on you.
Yes, you can.
I'm all in.
I'm the devil's mistress.
If we do this,
there's no mistakes.
Let's do it.
[Foreboding music plays]
[Ominous music continues]
[Music continues]
Be my devil's mistress tonight.
Or be maggot food, Carol.
Hmm.
Got it.
[Honking car]
So, how do you girls like L.A.?
All we seen of it is Hollywood.
Yeah, haven't even
been to the beach yet.
You girls will love our friends.
Their house is a mansion
with a gigantic pool.
It's boiling out. Why are
you wearing gloves?
[Whispering] Oh,
my hands are always cold.
[Suspenseful music]
Where are we? I don't
see any street lights.
[Suspenseful music playing]
You didn't say it would
take this long.
Look, we'll give
you your money back.
Just drop us off in Hollywood.
No, no, no, ladies.
When you live in L.A.
For a while, you'll realize,
it's very spread out.
[Ominous music playing]
Cut the stare lady
you're giving me chills.
You're a little plump,
aren't you?
You're not skinny yourself.
Are you calling me fat, bitch?
Oh God!
Look, I'm sorry I made
you hot around the collar,
but you started it.
Hey, hey,
tell her this isn't funny.
Tell her to stop.
Baby,
am I having a blast?
[Gunshot, splatters]
[Screams]
Huh!
[Gasping]
Okay, I'll do whatever you say.
Tell her I'll do
whatever you say.
Please! [Gunshot]
[Gasping]
Oh.
You're afraid I'll
shoot you, too?
Uhh.
[Breathing heavily]
Oh my, momma.
[Chuckles]
Hey.
You feel it?
It's like a bolt of lightning
ripping through me.
Every nerve ending is alive.
This is your first
divine moment,
and you only get one of them.
Baptized in fire.
We are partners is
that right? All the way?
Running and gunning, baby. This
is how a blood oath is made.
Prove it.
I'm speeding up.
[Slow rock music playing]
[Squelching]
[Moaning]
[Sawing]
[Squelching]
[Moaning softly]
[Squelching, ripping]
[Breathing heavily]
[Gasping]
[Whispering]
Oh my God.
[Whispering] - We did it.
Oh my God, we did it.
[Whispering]
[Breathing heavily]
What are we gonna
do with that thing?
Whatever you want.
[Ominous music playing]
[Plastic bag rustling]
[Door opening]
[Door closing]
Doug?
Oh
Hmm...
Hey, baby.
What do you got?
You were right.
It's time to send fatty
off in grand style.
[Laughing]
Imagine the cops busting
in our freezer door.
She's next to
the strawberry ice cream.
[Chuckles]
Why?
Cut the stare, lady.
You're giving me the chills.
[Laughing]
[Both laughing]
Hmm... hmm... hmm... hmm... hmm.
I'm gonna miss those
sweet lips of hers.
Whew.
Sometimes I wish we could
share our genius with others.
Come on.
They'd never understand.
We got ourselves
a special chromosome.
We're revolutionaries, you know.
Only interested in greatness.
[Both chuckle]
Eyes forward. Eyes forward,
I think we got the...
The boys in blue in back.
Just ah, where's the gun?
It's in my tampon bag.
I've never been in trouble.
Be calm, be calm.
Oh God.
What?
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ, Carol.
I told you not to defrost
that fucking thing.
I made up fatso's face
up like a Kewpie doll.
Just stay calm over
there. Put it down,
Put it down.
Keep your shoulders down.
Just keep breathing.
[Breathing deeply]
I think...
I think we got lucky.
They're more interested
in somebody else tonight.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Thank God.
[Relieved sigh]
[Chuckles nervously]
Whew
Lucky, lucky.
Grab some towels and see
if you can get that blood up.
[Sighs]
[Sniffles]
This whole thing's heating up.
I don't like it.
That murder mobile's gotta go.
Sell it.
We'll get something new.
I don't know, torch it,
insurance, something,
I don't know.
We didn't fuck up tonight.
Sure, shit feels like it.
Let's try something new.
A sex slave.
Your idea,
your rules.
A sex slave? Huh?
You can keep her in your
rental garage.
It's remote.
Yeah, thick walls.
She could scream all night.
Nobody hears her.
Some girls cry for help.
[Ominous music playing]
I beg for more.
[Ominous music continues]
You always this ready to bleed?
You like control, so take it.
[Foreboding music continues]
[Car pulling in]
[Tires screeching]
[Braking]
[Car door opening]
[Speaking Japanese]
[Screaming]
[Speaking in Japanese]
[Upbeat music]
[Music continues]
♪ I need a hand down babe, ♪
♪ starving for love. ♪
[Music fading]
[Foreboding music playing]
[Car engine rumbling]
Find me someone.
[Fast staccato music]
[Upbeat guitar music]
♪ I was lost and lonely man. ♪
♪ I had no life,
I had no plan. ♪
♪ You came along and
changed my way. ♪
[Whispering] - Take
the five. I know a place.
[Music fading]
They're healing.
They look a lot better
than last week.
You're not taking any
pictures off my ass, are you?
[Camera clicks]
No, absolutely not.
[Knocking]
There you are.
Nobody knew where you went.
I'm photographing
Mr. Petek's dermal ulcers.
I need a word.
My office.
I have twenty more patients
scheduled for photographs.
The photographs can wait.
Of course, Doctor.
[Clears throat]
She won't eat.
She's terrified of
her own daughter.
I saw her right
before your visit.
She was calm, smiling.
Now she cries nonstop.
If that was your mother,
how would you feel?
I followed protocol, doctor.
Did you?
Because I've got
nurses telling me that
you never stop talking
to her about that killer.
Sunset Slayer.
There's gonna be
an investigation top to bottom.
If I were you, I'd get a lawyer.
[Chattering in the background]
[Pool ball clinking]
Here comes trouble, mates.
[Footsteps]
Jack,
Can I speak with you, please?
It's important.
Please?
[Trunk creaking opening]
He makes me pack this for him
before he goes out hunting.
Calls it his kill bag.
Proves nothing.
I've known real killers.
That prissy bastard
wouldn't last a minute.
I've seen him.
Seen what?
I'm an accomplice.
You're helping a murderer?
He threatened to kill
me if I ratted him out.
Why tell me this?
Because you're next on the list.
He keeps talking about you,
and little Jenny.
The cocksucker
touches my daughter.
What did I do to him?
Says you used me took my money.
Why haven't the cops
caught this freak?
He's smart.
I gotta get back in.
If Doug targets you,
I can't stop him.
Figures you'd fall
in with a lunatic.
Two peas in a pod.
Meet me here after closing.
We'll figure something out.
[Whispering] I'm gonna
butterscotch you.
I'll have none a that.
[Lively guitar music]
[Pool balls clinking]
[Music continues]
♪ If someday,
the sun won't shine ♪
♪ no rain will fall,
the wind won't wind. ♪
♪ Maybe someday. ♪
♪ If some night
the river won't flow, ♪
♪ the roads won't bloom,
the trees won't grow, ♪
♪ Maybe someday. ♪
♪ Then we'll all be free. ♪
♪ If some day the hills
will crumble, ♪
♪ the grass will burn as
the buildings tumble. ♪
♪ Maybe someday ♪
♪ Maybe someday
it all come down, ♪
♪ to disappear
without a sound. ♪
♪ Maybe someday. ♪
Come on, let's get out of here.
[Door closing]
Oh, babe.
[Kissing]
See you tomorrow, sexy.
Bye, Jack.
Get in the car.
[Footsteps]
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
[Car engine starts]
[Car pulls over]
[Grunts]
Can't do it.
Why not?
Any money I make goes
to me bookies first.
Your daughter's life
is on the line, Jack.
a few thousand dollars
from you by next week,
or you won't like what happens.
If you thought you tricked
me into thinking,
Dougie was a psycho so
I'd pay your money back.
You're ditzier than I thought.
I'm desperate, Jack.
I'm about to lose my job.
Good.
Never understood why
they let a loony bird
be a nurse anyway.
Don't keep me waiting.
Ah, ah little romance, please.
Now it's romance you're after?
Jeanette laughed in my face,
when I asked about
her chemo treatments.
You lied through your teeth,
to get my twenty grand.
You'll get your money.
You wouldn't give a shit if
I was living in a cardboard box.
You crying again?
The little Scotsman gets
mean when he's waiting.
[Sobbing]
Hmm...
The Little Scotsman
knows what he needs.
There.
Guess you do have
a brain in there.
Huh. Get in your belly for Mama.
You're gonna do two
tickets to paradise.
[Both laughing]
Nobody does this as good as you.
Oh, Just you wait.
Nice to know you're good
for more than whining.
I'm gonna relax
you from top to bottom.
[Foreboding music playing]
[Gunshot, splatters]
[Ominous music continues]
[Gunshot]
Holy shit, I did it.
[Breathing heavily]
[Ominous music continues]
[Blood dripping]
I'm nutty, huh?
[Grunting]
I'm the crazy one?
[Grunting continues]
I'm nutty, huh!?
Crazy woman! [Screaming]
[Screaming]
♪ Walking up brodway
slippin down the Maine, ♪
♪ Met a policeman,
he asked my name. ♪
♪ Now mama, ♪
♪ wished I'd listened to you. ♪
♪ Threw me in a jailhouse
on my knees, ♪
♪ first thing I saw was
black eyed peas. ♪
♪ Now mama, ♪
♪ wished I'd listened to you. ♪
♪ I was a jailbird
all night long. ♪
♪ Mama came in and
took me home. ♪
♪ Now mama, ♪
♪ wished I'd listened to you. ♪
♪ I spanked on the butt
till I couldn't sit down. ♪
♪ Sit in my room,
I was prison bound. ♪
♪ Now mama, ♪
♪ wished I'd listened to you. ♪
[Ominous music playing]
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
I'm bringing Jack home.
Tell Murray to lick my balls.
He's not welcome here.
It's just his head, Doug.
With two bullets in it.
Idiot.
I'll be home in fifteen minutes.
Wait out front.
[Hangs up]
[Upbeat rock music playing]
[Plastic bag rustling]
[Music continues]
[Plastic bag rustles]
[Car pulling in]
Stop the car!
Stop the fuckin' car!
[Car engine dies]
Where is it?
Why the fuck?!
[Whimpering]
Things went sideways.
I just... I just
wondered what he...
No, no, no. You opened
your mouth, didn't you?
What the fuck did
you say about me?
Nothing, Doug. I...
Nothing?
I... I...
Get your fucking ass over here.
Scoot the fuck over!
[Dogs barking in distance]
[Car door closing]
[Car starting]
You fucking ruined everything!
[Car pulls away]
[Rock music playing]
[Music continues]
♪ Well I woke up in the morning
to an empty sheet, ♪
♪ ran out to the window
looking out on the street. ♪
♪ Saw my baby running
just as fast as she can. ♪
♪ Her hat on backwards and
in a suitcase in her hand. ♪
[Car door closing]
[Footsteps on gravel]
[Birds chirping in distance]
Sorry you missed it.
I didn't flinch.
This is your last mistake.
You hear me?
Loud and clear.
[Birds chirping]
Well if you're
gonna fucking do it.
Do it.
Adios, Jack!
[Thuds in a distance]
[Birds chirping]
I did it.
Last,
mistake.
And get in the fucking car.
[Footsteps on gravel]
I'm so sorry, Jack.
I'm so sorry.
[Slow country music
in the background]
Hey. make mine a highball.
Okay.
[Sighs]
Hi, Rick.
Carol,
what can I get you?
[Thuds]
A couple of high balls.
Nerves.
Sure.
Any news on Jack yet?
No ma'am,
it's been six days already.
He's probably shacked
up with some floozy.
Maybe so.
Anything is possible where
randy Jack is concerned.
You're right.
[Footsteps]
[Sighs]
[Country music playing
in the background]
[Glass thuds on table]
[Exhales deeply]
What's up?
You seem a little off.
All the memories are
hitting me at once.
Can we please leave?
No, we stick to the routine.
No exceptions.
[Sobbing quietly]
That damn Aussie is haunting me.
Cool your jets, Carol.
When I think of poor Jenny
growing up without a father?
[Sighs]
[Footsteps]
It's the girl he was
with last week.
She saw you together?
Jesus, Carol, we gotta go.
What?
Get up. We gotta go.
You have a light?
[Lighter clicks]
Thanks.
We found Jack's van.
The body's inside.
...fucking dead.
No! No! No!
Dead.
No! No!
[Sobbing loudly] Don't say that!
Don't say that!
[Shouting] No!
No!
[Sobbing]
Some son of a bitch took his...
No!
Cut his fucking head off!
Oh my God!
Stop it! Nooo!
♪ Now the fall, ♪
♪ And the fall, ♪
♪ bring sadness to the wind. ♪
♪ But can I say, ♪
♪ goodbye? ♪
[Guitar music playing]
[Tap running]
[Door knocking]
Ah, coming!
Oh.
[Knocking]
Coming.
Who is it?
LAPD. Open up.
Just a sec.
Ooh...
Uhh..
Doug?
Uh... - What?
LAPD is at the door.
What?
Uh.. They're at the door.
Did you what uh what? Uh...
Let them in,
Doug, what's going on?
Let them in. admit to nothing.
Hmm, ah!
Your maid do something?
Just,
she's a dumbass.
LAPD.
Carol Bundy?
Yeah.
What can I do for you?
We have some questions
we need to ask you.
Does Doug Clark live here also?
Uh yes.
[Upbeat country music playing]
♪ Oh bartender, bartender, ♪
♪ set him up again. ♪
♪ I'm only two whiskeys ♪
♪ away from the end. ♪
♪ And soon there will be, ♪
♪ a blurred memory ♪
♪ Of the morning she woke up, ♪
♪ and had to be free. ♪
♪ Just two more
shots of double, ♪
♪ ta-da! ♪
How did my life
turn out like this?
Will you please relax?
There's not enough
evidence to hold us.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Wake up!
Pierce is looking at me like
I'm already strapped
to a fucking gurney.
No, I'm
No, I'm a fucking failure.
Cheer up, Doug.
All is not lost.
Yes, it is.
I mean, I can't believe
I voted to have the fucking
death penalty reinstated.
I'm a fucking walking dead man.
No, I'm... I'm...
[Breathing heavily]
Oh.
Carol.
Sweet Carol.
[Laughing]
We were fucking doomed
from the start, so...
That's that.
[Car engine starts]
[Car pulling away]
[Car engine roaring]
Don't touch the rest
of my shit in here.
I'll be back for it.
You're upset now,
but one day you'll miss
having me in your corner.
Fuck.
You haven't learned yet?
I don't have any
fucking corners.
Blood oaths are forever,
remember?
Just stay. Let's talk.
Don't do something
you're gonna regret.
Let's talk. - Shut up!
Let's talk baby!
Shut up! Take another pill.
Pull out your fucking vibrator.
You'll be fine.
[Glass thuds on counter]
Please don't leave.
I need you!
[Footsteps]
[Melancholic music playing]
[Sobbing]
Nothing left to take.
♪ Ain't no love, ♪
♪ in this house. ♪
♪ that we live in. ♪
♪ Ain't no affection ♪
♪ to be found, ♪
in these rooms.
♪ Ain't no love ♪
♪ in this house, ♪
♪ that we live in. ♪
♪ Just two strangers ♪
♪ who continue, ♪
♪ to pretend. ♪
This morning,
we're going to get a take, OK?
Here we go.
[Piano music starts]
[Knocking]
Ah...
[Piano playing in
the background]
Oh. Hang on a sec,
Tommy. Scratch that.
I need a minute.
[Recorder clicking]
Come in!
Jesus.
You look like a rug
munching dyke.
Will you please put
your arms around me?
Showing up here was a really
fucking boneheaded move.
Please come home.
Nah! - I'll do anything
No!
I prefer to keep my fucking head
attached to my fucking body.
Thank you very much.
I got a job to do. Please leave.
[Sobbing]
I'd rather be in jail
than live without you.
[Sobbing loudly]
I knocked myself out
trying to please you.
Nobody fucking asked you to!
You volunteered!
My only regret is
I didn't bleed
you that divorce money
before Jack did.
Now, get out.
Then I'll call the cops
confess what I'd done.
Oh, you fucking would,
wouldn't you,
you crazy fucking cunt?
You would blow up
your fucking life
well you're not fucking
blowing up mine.
[Sobbing]
Not fucking blowing up mine.
Now get the fuck out of here.
[Door closing]
[Clears nose]
It's been a morning, Tommy.
We got it figured out.
Technical issues are good.
[Piano playing]
[Piano continues]
Well it's been a lot of stuff on
the news lately about these,
Uh...
Sunset murders?
Are you well-versed
in these killings?
Mm-hmm, I am.
Well,
Well, detective,
would you like to know
who's been committing them?
Sure.
[Sobbing] I've done
one of my own.
Calm down.
Let's take it from
the beginning.
And. And...
Then we left
the head in an alley.
He's fallen apart over it.
I'm just plain sick of it.
He wants to continue this,
and continue this.
And then I...
I...
I was reluctant partner in
the hands of a maniac,
that overwhelmed me.
The whole thing, like a...
...a fantasy that's
spiraled out of control.
[Closing bottle]
[Ominous music playing]
[Metal rattles]
[Breathing heavily]
[Ominous music continues]
[Knock on door]
[Box rattles]
Tommy!
Get him in the booth!
[Ominous music continues]
[Knocking]
Carol Bundy?
Yes.
Turn around.
You're under arrest.
Put your hands up.
Easy, please.
I'm disabled.
Bring em down.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Everything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
If you can't afford an attorney,
one will be provided.
Do you understand your rights?
Yes.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
[Footsteps]
You fucking bitch.
You killed my husband!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
♪ Well, I woke up
in the morning ♪
♪ to an empty sheet. ♪
♪ Ran out to the window
looking out on the street. ♪
Okay,
session 14, take 2.
♪ [Piano playing
Moonlight Sonata] ♪
Detectives?
You're under arrest, Doug.
[Cuffs clinking]
[Piano playing in
the background]
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be held against
you in the court of law.
♪ [Moonlight sonata fades] ♪
[Long guitar string playing]
[Recorder clicks, humming]
Search wherever you want,
detectives.
[Clears throat]
The sooner we get
this over, the better.
I barely knew Jack.
I had no reason to hurt him.
Ever pick up a prostitute?
What's that got to do
with Carol killing someone?
Just answer the question.
Okay.
On occasion,
if I want to get up
at an ego boost,
I'll pick up a low-grade
hooker, sure.
Ever heard of necrophilia?
Yeah.
And?
Not my cup of tea.
[Huffs]
Doug
We found the gun.
I want a lawyer.
[Smirks]
[Taps shoulder] - Sit tight.
[Door closes]
Doug didn't make me do anything,
against my will.
Have you taken him into custody?
Yeah, we have.
He must be furious.
Do you have any regrets
over what's happening,
I mean...
About the people
that you and Clark hurt?
Of course I do.
It's the stuff I'll
beat myself up
about the rest of my life.
However...
However what?
The honest truth.
Yeah.
It's fun to kill.
And if I could run loose,
I'd probably do it again.
[Sighs]
It's going to sound crazy,
and I don't think I'm
that crazy, but...
It's a kick.
Like riding a roller coaster.
You know,
They say there's relief,
when something like this ends.
I don't agree with that.
Not at all.
You sit tight.
We'll be right back.
Uh...hmm.
[Slow guitar string playing]
Name's Doug Clark
[Music continues]
[Camera clicks]
[Upbeat country music playing]
♪ Walking the streets
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ Lord, hallelujah. ♪
♪ The city's filled
with dreamers, ♪
♪ searching for that gold. ♪
♪ These streets are
filled with sinners, ♪
♪Bargaining for your soul. ♪
♪ The devil's on the corner, ♪
♪ Selling tickets to his show. ♪
♪ I'm in the middle, ♪
♪ But I stay out through I go. ♪
♪ A farm boy in the city, ♪
♪ there's a bird
without a wing. ♪
♪ Try to fly but not too high, ♪
♪ put it on the string. ♪
♪ And all the people
around it, ♪
♪ Our party's time to fall. ♪
♪ Just jump back up
with a big old smile ♪
♪ when you hear
your mama call. ♪
♪ Oh, Mama, ♪
♪ I promise I'll be good. ♪
♪ I promise you'll be good. ♪
♪ I'll send you back
to Coast Guard, ♪
♪ all the way from Hollywood. ♪
♪ Walking the streets
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ walking the streets
of Hollywood. ♪
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ Lord hallelujah. ♪
♪ Walking the streets
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ Lord hallelujah. ♪
♪ Walking the streets
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ Lord hallelujah. ♪
♪ Walking the streets
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ up and down divine. ♪
♪ Up and down the sunset. ♪
♪ Walking the streets
filled with fire. ♪
of Hollywood, ♪
♪ Walk... Walk...
Walk... Walk... ♪
♪ Walking the streets,
walking the streets. ♪
[Music continues]
[Music fades]
♪ [Moonlight Sonata Playing] ♪
♪ But in the morning, ♪
♪ Come rain or shine, ♪
♪ I'll be gone. ♪
[End]